Johnny Otis Collection, 1949-2012 SC 106
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Radio Airchecks, Johnny Otis Show
  - 4.2. KPFK (Los Angeles) and KPFA (Berkeley), 1982-1994
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-07-31; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Bernie Pearl
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Blind Willie Johnson, Charles Brown, H-Bomb Ferguson, Chuck Jackson, Irma Thomas, Mills Brothers, Ravens, Jimmy Reed, Harmonica Fats, Ray Charles, and LaVern Baker. Otis and Pearl talk about Charles Brown and The Ravens first time on stage with Otis.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, LaVern Baker, Jimmy & Jeannie Cheatham, and Barbara Moore. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 5: Otis and friends take phone calls. Otis plays the music of Fats Domino, Little Richard, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, Sam Cooker, Louie Jordan, Jimmie Lunceford, B.B. King, Billie Holiday, and Count Basie.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Count Basie, Bobby Bland, Duke Ellington, and Ike & Tine Turner.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-08-07; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      OT 10115; OT 10116; OT 10117; OT 10118; OT 10119; OT 10120
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j23603x313
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Johnnie Taylor, Ray Charles, Little Walter, Count Basie, T-Bone Walker, Lloyd Price, Dinah Washington, and the Clovers.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the Clovers, LaVern Baker, Big Joe Turner, Charles Brown, Bull Moose Jackson, Lee Dorsey, Ernie K-Doe, Sonny Terry & Brownie McGhee, and Duke Ellington feat. Al Hibbler. Otis talks about recent death of Bull Moose Jackson.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Duke Ellington feat. Al Hibbler, Brad Pie, Etta James, Orioles, Staple Singers, Fats Domino, Rev. Claude Jeter, Billie Holiday, and Robert Johnson. Live blues performances from Brad Pie. Otis talks to Pie about his background.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Robert Johnson, Freddy King, Lil Green, Bull Moose Jackson, Amos Milburn, and B.B. King. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Amos Milburn, B.B. King, Aretha Franklin, Jimmy Reed, Louis Jordan, Linda Hopkins, and Jimmy Rogers. Otis talks about discovering Linda Hopkins.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Rogers, Albert King, the Coasters, Marvin Gaye, Roy Milton, Muddy Waters, Nat Cole, and LaVern Baker.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-08-14; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Bernie Pearl, Harmonica Fats, John Patton, Curtis Griffith
      OT 10121; OT 10122; OT 10123; OT 10124; OT 10125; OT 10126
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x51h543c72
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Chuck Berry, Louis Jordan, Otis Redding, Joe Turner, Jimmy Reed, Aretha Franklin, Ray Charles, Sonny Terry & Brownie McGhee, Billie Holiday, and Lil Green.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Lil Green, B.B. King, Tampa Red, Etta James, Elmore James, Koko Taylor, Harmonica Fats, and Bernie Pearl & Harmonica Fats. Live performances by Harmonica Fats and Bernie Pearl.
      Tape 3: Live performance by Bernie Pearl and Harmonica Fats. Otis plays the music of Prof. Alex Bradford, Dorothy Love Coates, Louis Armstrong, Julia Lee, Smokey Wilson, Albert Collins, Lightnin' Hopkins, and Tina Turner. Otis and friends talk about Black music of the past and present, then take phone calls.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Coasters, Clyde McPhatter, Fats Domino, and Wilson Pickett. Live performance of "Stormy Monday Blues" by Pearl, Harmonica Fats and Curtis Griffith. Pearl talks about how Griffith inspired him to keep playing the blues.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Wilson Pickett, and Johnny Otis feat. Ramona and Jackie Payne.
      Tape 6: Otis closes the show.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Count Basie's Birthday, 1989-08-21; 4 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      OT 10127; OT 10128; OT 10129; OT 10130
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k81j532s40
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Lowell Fulson, Lionel Hampton, Lightnin' Hopkins, Count Basie, Aretha Franklin, Smokey Hogg, Duke Ellington, Slim Harpo, John Lee Hooker, Archie Brownlee & the Five Blind Boys of Mississippi, Al Green, Ella Fitzgerald, Billie Holiday, Lloyd Price, and Otis Redding. Otis talks about poverty and environmental issues.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Otis Redding, Joe Jones, Sam & Dave, B.B. King, James Brown, Count Basie, Charlie Christian, Johnny Otis, Johnny Otis feat. Ramona & Jackie Payne, and Johnny Otis feat. LaDee Streeter.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Johnny Otis feat. LaDee Streeter, Johnny Otis feat. Ramona, Johnny Otis, Smokey Robinson & the Miracles, Marvin Gaye, Gene Krupa, Jimmie Lunceford, Calvin Bose, Little Willie John, Big Maybelle, Percy Mayfield, Bo Diddley, Heartbeats, Count Basie, El Dorados, and the Clovers. Johnny Otis & Brad Pie perform live.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Clovers, Floyd Ray, Jimmy Reed, and Ray Charles.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-08-29; 4 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Andy McKay
      OT 10131; OT 10132; OT 10133; OT 10134
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w22v145c45
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan & Johnny Otis, Ruth Brown, Aretha Franklin, Muddy Waters, Jody Williams, Little Walter, Paul Gayten, Fontella Bass, and Al Green.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Al Green, Robert Nighthawk, Big Three Trio, Big Joe Turner, Muddy Waters & James Cotton, Billy Stewart, Koko Taylor, Bo Diddley, Elmore James, Mitty Collier, Jackie Brenston, Dizzy Gillespie, Johnny Otis feat. Ramona, and Lee Andrews & the Hearts.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Johnny Otis feat. Ramona, Lee Andrews & the Hearts, Clarence Henry, Ramsey Lewis, Lowell Fulson, Chuck Berry, Ann Peebles, Fats Waller, Billie Holiday, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, Bobby Bland, Charlie Parker, Paul Williams, Dominoes, Etta James, Dirty Red, B.B. King, and Joe Liggins.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Duke Ellington, Ray Charles, King Curtis, Otis Redding, Wilson Pickett, Roscoe Gordon, and Jimmy Reed.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-09-04; 4 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      OT 10135; OT 10136; OT 10137; OT 10138
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/524j62zq0x
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of the Four Tops, Otis Redding, Etta James, Jay McShann, Coasters, Ray Charles, Clovers, Lloyd Price, Dinah Washington, Eddie Floyd, Joe Liggins, B.B. King, Bessie Smith, Brad Pie, and the Fiestas. Live performance from Brad Pie ("Blues in B Natural").
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the Fiestas, Martha & the Vandellas, Louis Armstrong, Wilbert Harrison, Sam & Dave, Wilson Pickett, Silhouettes, Billie Holiday, Marvelettes, Aretha Franklin, Lee Dorsey, Champion Jack DuPree, Ray Charles, and Slim & Slam.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Slim & Slam, Muddy Waters, Count Basie, Little Willie John, Swallows, Fats Waller, Johnny Otis, Bardu Ali, & Kathy Cooper, Chuck Berry, Nat Cole, Five Blind Boys, Jackie Wilson, and Sam Cooke.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Five Blind Boys, Jackie Wilson, Sam Cooke, Gary "U.S." Bonds, Sarah Vaughan, Delta Rhythm Boys, Jimmy Reed, and Hank Ballard & the Midnighters.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Songs with "Love" in the Title, 1989-09-11; 3 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Terry Carter, Brad Pie
      OT 10139; OT 10140; OT 10141
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x21t44w439
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Mickey & Sylvia, Clyde McPhatter, Bobby Bland, Little Junior Parker, Supremes, Drifters, Billie Holiday, Duke Ellington, Little Esther Phillips, Paul Gayten, Muddy Waters, Bessie Smith, Brad Pie, Monotones, and Aretha Franklin. Live performance from Brad Pie ("Blues in E"). Otis interviews Terry Carter (via telephone) about his documentary, "A Duke Named Ellington."
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Johnny Otis feat. Charles Williams, LaVern Baker, Brad Pie, Freddie King, Otis Redding, Don Gardener & Dee Dee Ford, Charles Brown, Ray Charles, Percy Sledge, Big Joe Turner, Sam & Dave, Johnny Otis & Brad Pie, Jimmy Reed, Jerry Butler, and Johnny Otis feat. Mel Walker & Ada Wilson. Live performance from Brad Pie and Otis ("Breakfast Blues" and "Love Makes Me Do Foolish Things"). Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Johnny Otis feat. Mel Walker & Ada Wilson, Etta James, Fats Domino, Marvin Gaye, Louis Armstrong, Dizzy Gillespie, Bo Diddley, Preston Love, Dinah Washington, Clovers, Johnnie Taylor, John Lee Hooker, Shirelles, Ruth Brown, Teen Queens, and Jesse Belvin. Otis and friends talk about Pakistani food with the show's engineer.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-09-18; 4 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      OT 10142; OT 10143; OT 10144; OT 10145
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b49425rp4j
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Wilson Pickett, Coasters, Joe Turner, Sam & Dave, Jimmy Reed, Preston Love, Joon Yamagichi & Shuggie Otis, Aretha Franklin, Count Basie, Dinah Washington, Preston Love, Lowell Fulson, and Muddy Waters. Otis and friends talk about fishing.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Otis Redding and Irma Thomas.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of the Four Tops, Brook Benton, Ella Fitzgerald, Billie Holiday, Clyde McPhatter & the Drifters, Claude Cloud, Chuck Berry, Little Willie John, Esther Phillips, Louis Jordan, Brad Pie, Isley Brothers, Joe Tex, Roy Eldridge, Eddie Vinson & Cootie Williams, Barbara George, and Aaron Neville; Live performance from Brad Pie. Otis talks about discovering Little Willie John and signing him to King Records.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Barbara George, Aaron Neville, and Count Basie.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Irving Berlin Tribute, 1989-09-25; 4 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): June Yamagishi, Shuggie Otis, Brad Pie
      OT 10146; OT 10147; OT 10148; OT 10149
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n59q08c14n
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Lavern Baker, Frank Cully, Little Richard, Ray Charles, Drifters, Howlin' Wolf, Muddy Waters, Mills Brothers, Ella Fitzgerald, Bo Diddley, Fats Domino, Temptations, Al Green, Shuggie Otis, and Aretha Franklin. Live performance from Shuggie Otis.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Impressions, June Yamagishi feat. Shuggie Otis, Yamagishi & Bobby Womack, Count Basie, Lloyd Price, Swan Silvertones, Billie Holiday, and Otis Redding. Otis interviews Yamagishi about his recent tour in Japan and how he got started in blues. Live blues performances from Yamagishi and Shuggie Otis.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Otis Redding, Taj Mahal, B.B. King, Silhouettes, Robert Parker, Wild Tchoupitoulas, Joe Turner feat. Elmore James, June Yamagishi, Brad Pie, & Johnny Otis, Jimmy Reed, Gladys Knight & the Pips, Louis Armstrong, Louis Jordan, Cleo Brown, Clovers, Lee Allen, T-Bone Walker, and Julia Lee. Live blues performances by Yamagishi and Pie ("I Heard It Through the Grapevine" and "T-Bone Walker Blues"). Otis talks about upcoming Bernie Pearl show.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Julia Lee.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Food Related Songs, 1989-10-02; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Bernie Pearl, Tony Matthews, Brad Pie
      OT 10150; OT 10151; OT 10152; OT 10153; OT 10154; OT 10155
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s75d37c20m
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Lloyd Price, Robins, LaVern Baker, Louis Jordan, Edith Johnson, Tony Matthews, Pee Wee Crayton. Otis and Pearl discuss John Collins, Pee Wee Crayton and his version of "Blues After Hours," and talk to Matthews about his background.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Pee Wee Crayton, Marvelettes, Marvin & Johnny, King Curtis, Amos Milburn, Fats Domino, Booker T & the M.G.'s, and Little Richard. Otis talks to Matthews about his musical influences, the state of blues music, and Otis's upcoming album.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Booker T & the M.G.'s, Little Richard, Olympics, Hank Williams, Little Milton, Slim Gaillard, and Jesse Stone. Live performance from Tony Matthews ("Who's Lovin' You Tonight"). Otis and guests promote an upcoming blues concert and share memories of Pee Wee Crayton.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Jesse Stone, Butterbeans and Susie, Eddie Vinson, Four Tops, and Otis Redding. Live performance by Pie and Matthews. Otis and guests take phone calls.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Otis Redding, Big Maybelle, Dinah Washington, Billy Eckstine, Swallows, Tony Matthews, B.B. King, and Duke Ellington. Bernie Pearl performs live.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Duke Ellington, Billie Holiday, Preston Love & Shuggie Otis, Johnny Otis, Coasters, Nat King Cole, and Louis Jordan. Matthews and Pearl perform live.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-10-09; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Steve Rosier, John Patton, Brad Pie
      OT 10156; OT 10157; OT 10158; OT 10159; OT 10160; OT 10161
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/890r76mn8f
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Hal Singer, Temptations, Lloyd Price, Jimmy Reed, Bobby Bland, Big Joe Turner & Elmore James, Little Willie John, and Jimmie Lunceford.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Jimmie Lunceford, Ray Charles, Ruth Brown, Johnny Otis, Hank Ballard, and Marvelettes. Otis talks about Ray Charles's hit "Don't You Know Baby," how he learned to "roll" on the drums and why.
      Tape 3: Otis talks about the importance of traditional music within cultures and about musical tastes today. Otis plays the music of Billie Holiday, Duke Ellington, Fats Domino, Don Gardner & Dee Dee Ford, Robert Johnson, King Curtis, and Chuck Berry.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Chuck Berry, Wilson Pickett, Count Basie, Johnny Otis, Aretha Franklin, and Joe Simon. Otis and friends discuss their favorite trumpet players.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Joe Simon, Fats Waller, Slim & Slam, Dixie Cups, and Chris Kenner.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Chris Kenner, Little Lester, Louis Jordan, Little Walter, B.B. King, Coasters, and Ink Spots.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-10-16; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Gerald Wilson, Barbara Moore, Brad Pie, John Patton
      OT 10162; OT 10163; OT 10164; OT 10165; OT 10166; OT 10167
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g05f36bd64
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Jay McShann, Coasters, Otis Redding, Ray Charles, Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson, B.B. King, Slim Harpo, Chuck Berry, and Little Willie John.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Little Willie John, Four Deuces, Sam & Dave, Staple Singers, Marvin Gaye, and Dinah Washington. Otis welcomes Wilson, who discusses his new album, Lester Young, the Greystone Ballroom, and Edwin Wilcox.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Gerald Wilson, Barbara Moore, Johnny Otis, Swan Silvertones, and Dorothy Love Coates & the Gospel Harmonettes. Otis talks with Gerald Wilson and Barbara Moore about their influences, Wilson's band and their version of "Flying Home."
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Swan Silvertones, Dorothy Love Coates & the Gospel Harmonettes, Barbara Moore, Gerald Wilson, and Big Joe Turner. Live performance by Brad Pie and Barbara Moore ("Thinkin' and Drinkin'"). Otis and Wilson discuss jazz musicians who also play blues.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Big Joe Turner, Smokey Hogg, John Lee Hooker, Lowell Fulson, and Etta James.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Etta James, Gerald Wilson, and Bobby Bland. Live performance segments featuring Johnny Otis with Gerald Wilson. Otis and Wilson discuss Otis's vibes and playing multiple instruments.
      Tape 7: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, the Temptations, the Spinners, Bob & Earl, Irma Thomas, the Fiestas, the Moonglows, Wilbert Harrison, and Fontella Bass.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-10-23; 5 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): John Patton
      OT 10169; OT 10170; OT 10171; OT 10172; OT 10173
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/069821ns2j
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Temptations, Spinners, Bob & Earl, Irma Thomas, Fiestas, Moonglows, Wilbert Harrison, and Fontella Bass.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Fontella Bass, Dizzy Gillespie, Impressions, Little Milton, Louisiana Red, James Brown, Marvin Gaye & Tammi Terrell, and Lil Green. Otis and Patton talk about James Brown.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Lil Green, Duke Ellington, Wynonie Harris, Percy Mayfield, Drifters, and Joe Tex. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 4: Otis and friends take phone calls. Otis plays the music of Little Walter, Jimmy Nelson, Johnny Otis, LaVern Baker, and Paul Kelly.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Paul Kelly, Ella & Buddy Johnson, Louis Jordan, Elmore James, Bobby Parker, Count Basie, Jimmie Lunceford, and Ray Charles.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, Katie Webster, Wilson Pickett, Barbara Lynn, Alan Toussaint, Otis Redding, Joe Turner, and Amos Milburn. Otis promotes upcoming blues gig.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Songs About Animals, 1989-11-06; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Brad Pie
      OT 10174; OT 10175; OT 10176; OT 10177; OT 10178; OT 10179
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n300994h20
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Joe Turner, Howlin' Wolf, Ravens, Jr. Walker & the All-Stars, Slim Green & the Cats from Fresno, Johnny Otis, Little Junior Parker, James Brown, and Louis Jordan.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan, Preston Love feat. Shuggie Otis, Smokey Robinson & the Miracles, Johnny Otis, Little Walter & the Nightcats, Joe Swift, Coasters, Count Basie, and Jackie Wilson. Brad Pie talks with Otis and plays guitar.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Jackie Wilson, Major Lance, Jewel Akens, Tampa Red, and Slim Harpo. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Slim Harpo, Duke Ellington, Muddy Waters, Jackie Lee, Taj Mahal, Bobby Day, Inez & Charlie Foxx, and Rufus Thomas. Otis and friends talk about their favorite animals.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Rufus Thomas, Big Mama Thornton, Louis Armstrong, Rosetta Crawford, Coasters, Otis Redding, Wilson Pickett, Lee Dorsey, Chuck Berry, and Big Maybelle.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Big Maybelle, Tony Allen, the Clovers, Clarence "Frogman" Henry, Charlie Parker, Amos Milburn, Joe Williams & Sonny Boy Williamson, and Bo Diddley.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Songs or Artists with Plants in their Name, 1989-11-13; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 10180; OT 10181; OT 10182; OT 10183; OT 10184; OT 10185
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/079524qx5b
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Eddie Floyd, Percy Sledge, Clovers, Big Joe Turner, Etta James, Cadets, Louis Armstrong, Fats Waller, Booker T. & the MGs.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the Coasters, Fats Domino, Gladys Knight & the Pips, Count Basie, Ivy Anderson, Chuck Berry, Ray Charles, B.B. King, Willie Mabon, and Louis Jordan.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan, Billie Holiday, Marvin & Johnny, Brenton Wood, Jr. Walker & the All-Stars. Otis and friends discuss racism and blaming minorities for America's social ills.
      Tape 4: Otis and friends take phone calls. Otis plays the music of Wilson Pickett, Johnny Otis, Little Miss Cornshucks, Harlemaires, Hazel Scott, and Little Richard.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of the Meters, Nutmegs, Richard Berry, Ben E. King, Velvelettes, Cleo Brown, Charlie Parker, Baron & the Blue River Band, John Lee Hooker, Maceo Woods, and the Raspberries. Otis talks about Cleo Brown.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Maceo Woods, Raspberries, King Curtis, Herb Jeffries, Johnny Otis & Eddie Vinson, Preston Love feat. Shuggie Otis, and Ray Charles.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Songs with Women's Names in the Title, 1989-11-20; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Ramona, Brad Pie, Shuggie Otis
      OT 10186; OT 10187; OT 10188; OT 10189; OT 10190; OT 10191
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b88q382645
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Little Richard, Lionel Hampton, Clovers, Tampa Red, Fats Domino, Little Jr. Parker, Big Maybelle, Larry Williams, and Ray Charles.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, Drifters, Charlie Parker, Chuck Berry, Big Joe Turner, Fats Waller, Louis Jordan, Johnny Otis, and Eddie Vinson.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Eddie Vinson, Joe Liggins, Mills Brothers, Swan Silvertones, Billie Holiday, and Johnny Otis feat. Ramona. Live performance with Ramona, Brad Pie and Shuggie Otis.
      Tape 4: Live performance with Ramona, Brad Pie and Shuggie Otis. Otis plays the music of Brother Bones, Buster Brown, T-Bone Walker, Professor Longhair, Ike & Tine Turner, and Stevie Wonder.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, Bobby Day, Nat Cole, Jimmie Lunceford, Lloyd Price, Wilson Pickett, Don & Dewey, Olympics, and B.B. King. Otis and friends talk about women they would like to run for President.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of B.B. King, Charles Brown, Four Tops, Young Jessie, Coasters, Otis Redding, Duke Ellington, Ravens, and Leadbelly.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-12-04; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 10192; OT 10193; OT 10194; OT 10195; OT 10196; OT 10197
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x719607j16
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Etta James, Sam & Dave, Lionel Hampton, Four Deuces, Little Junior Parker, Fats Domino, Son House, and the Monotones. Otis and friends talk about the lack of a blues radio station.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the Monotones, Muddy Waters, Count Basie, Brook Benton, Aretha Franklin, Clyde McPhatter & the Drifters, and Charlie Byrd. Otis and friends talk about Black artists getting cheated out of royalties, Charlie Byrd, the roots of jazz, and Sly Stone.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Sly Stone, B.B. King, Johnny Otis, and Little Willie John.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Howlin' Wolf, Hank Ballard, Bessie Smith, Joe Tex, Fats Waller, Duke Ellington, Bobby Bland, and Billie Holiday.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Billie Holiday, Ray Charles, Martha & the Vandellas, Barbara Lynn, Louis Jordan, King Curtis, Sweet Inspirations, Flamingos, Jackie Wilson, and Charles Brown. Otis and friends talk about what they were doing in 1952.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Charles Brown, Big Joe Turner, Johnny Otis feat. Little Esther, Marvin Gaye, Bobby Marchand, Louis Armstrong, Solomon Burke, and Ruth Brown.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-12-11; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 10198; OT 10199; OT 10200; OT 10201; OT 10202; OT 10203
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/643999td81
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan, Sonny Terry & Brownie McGhee, Stevie Wonder, Lil Green, Roy Hamilton, Drifters, Johnny Otis, and Diane Reeves.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Diane Reeves, Sam & Dave, Al Green, King Curtis, Little Junior Parker, Albert King, Ruth Brown, Chuck Willis, and Joe Turner.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Joe Turner, Aretha Franklin, Take 6, Swan Silvertones, and Jimmie Lunceford. Otis and friends take phone calls.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Jimmie Lunceford, Jimmy Reed, Sam Cooke, B.B. King, Little Willie John, Johnny Otis, Charles Brown, Billie Holiday, and Ella Fitzgerald.